너희 남자들이 이해를
못하는 게 있는데
You don't understand.
For us, kissing is as
important as any part.
어떤 과정 못지 않게
키스가 중요하다는 거야
Yeah, right!
아무렴
진짜?
You serious?
그럼
Oh, yeah.
키스가 시작이라는 걸
알아야지
-Everything is in that first kiss.
-Absolutely.
맞아
그렇겠지
키스는 오프닝 같은 거야
For us, kissing's an opening act...
...Iike the comedian
you have to sit through...
개그쇼 같은 데 갔을 때
자리에 앉아 있으면
... before Pink Floyd comes out.
'핑크 플로이드' 음악이
나오잖아
그래, 우리가 그 개그맨을
싫어해서가 아니라
And it's not that
we don't like the comedian.
그냥... 그러니까 우린
티켓을 안 살 뿐이지
It's just that that's not
why we bought the ticket.
콘서트가 끝난 다음에
쇼가 잘됐든 못됐든
The problem is, no matter
how great the show was...
여자들은 그 개그맨을
다시 보고 싶어 안달하지만
...you girls are looking
for the comedian again.
우린 잠 안 자려고 두 눈
부릅뜨고 있단 걸 알아줘
We' re in the car, fighting traffic,
just trying to stay awake.
충고 한 마디 할까?
그 개그맨을 찾아서 데려와
Word of advice:
Bring back the comedian.
안 그럼 다음엔 집에서
혼자 앨범 듣게 할 테니까
Or next time you'll find yourself
listening to that album alone.
섹스 얘기하는 거 아니었어?
Are we still talking about sex?
The One With the Sonogram at the End
선사시대 박물관
아니, 그런 얘기가 아니라
좀 화난 것 같지 않아요?
No, it's good. It is good.
It's just that-- Doesn't she seem
a little angry?
의견 대립이 있는 거죠
Well, she has issues.
그래요?
Does she?
바람둥이 남편이랑
결혼했거든요
T ry to live with " Mr. I' m Evolving. "
남편이 다른 여자랑 클럽에서
노닥거리는 동안
He's out while she's home getting
the mastodon smell out of the carpet.
부인은 집에 앉아서 코끼리
발냄새나 맡고 있는 거죠
이 사람들은 동굴에 살아요
Marsha, see, these are cave people.
의견 대립이라야 이런 거겠죠
'저것 봐, 빙하가 다가오고 있어'
Okay, they have issues like:
"Gee, that glacier's
getting kind of close. "
Speaking of issues,
isn't that your ex-wife?
저 분 당신 전 부인
아닌가요?
네? 아뇨
-No.
-Yes, it is. Carol, hi!
맞잖아요,
캐롤, 안녕!
정말 그러네
빙하시대에 다시 만나죠
Okay. Yes, it is.
I'll catch up with you in the lce Age.
- 인사해도 돼요?
- 아뇨
-Can I stay?
-No.
- 안녕
-Hi.
잘못 찾아온 거야?
-ls this a bad time?
-No, it's...
아니
석기 시대에 온 걸 환영해
...the Stone Age.
좋아 보이는군
기분 나쁜데
You look great. I hate that.
미안해, 고맙고
Sorry. Thanks. You look good too.
당신도 좋아 보여
그거야 여기 서 있으니까
Well, you know,
in here, anyone who...
두 발로 서서...
...stands erect....
어때? 요즘도...
-What's new? Still a--
-A lesbian?
- 레즈비언이냐고?
- 글쎄...
물론 그렇겠지
You never know. How's the family?
근데, 가족들은 어때?
마티는 여전히 편집증이야
-Marty's still totally paranoid.
-Carol, why are you here?
- 그래서...
- 여긴 웬 일이야, 캐롤?
- 나 임신했어
- 임신?
-l' m pregnant.
-Pregnant.
She didn 't leave
in such a hurry after all.
그렇게 급하게 떠난 것
같지는 않은데
세사람만 모이면 어디든
저렇게 오해가 생긴다니까
This is the Three 's Company episode
with a misunderstanding.
그럼 볼 필요도 없겠네
Then I've already seen this one.
다 마셨지?
Are you through with that?
천천히 음미하면서 마셔서
미안해
Sorry, the swallowing slowed me down.
이 작은 종이 뭉치
누구 거야?
Whose ball of paper is this?
내 걸 거야
Mine. I wrote a note to myself,
then I didn't need it.
나한테 편지 쓴 건데 종이가
필요없을 것 같아서 구겼어
So I balled it up
and now I wish I was dead.
미안해서 죽어버리고 싶다
아까 베개 부풀렸잖아
She already fluffed that pillow.
You already fluffed-- It's fine.
모니카, 아까 했는데
아니, 계속해
미안해, 괜히 트집잡힐까봐
걱정돼서 그래
I just don't wanna give them
any more ammunition.
부모님이 애들 베개 갖고
트집 잡으면 얼마나 무서운데
Parents can be cruel about
the flatness of a child's pillow.
그만 좀 해
Relax, you do this every time.
The place looks great.
부모님 오실 때마다 이러니...
내 눈엔 좋기만 하다
You got a lasagna here
that looks good enough...
라자냐도 있지, 맛있겠다
손대면 안되겠지?
...to avoid touching.
모니카, 안녕
Monica? Hi!
모니카, 너 무서워
Monica, you' re scaring me.
너 잔뜩 긴장한 거 알아?
나쁜 쪽으로 말야
I mean, you' re all chaotic
and twirly, you know?
Not in a good way.
괜찮아
Calm down. You don't see Ross
getting twirly every time they come.
로스는 부모님 오셔도
너처럼 잔뜩 긴장하진 않잖아
그야 부모님은 오빠를
철썩같이 믿고 있으니까
That's because my parents think
Ross can do no wrong.
왕자님이잖아
You see, he's "The Prince. "
내가 태어나기 전에 아마
축하공연도 해 주셨을 걸
They had some big ceremony
before I was born.
왜?
-What?
-Ugly Naked Guy got a ThighMaster.
못난이 벌거숭이가
종아리 털 밀고 있어
내 약혼 반지 못 봤니?
-Has anybody seen my engagement ring?
-It's beautiful.
봤어, 예쁘더라
맙소사, 안돼, 맙소사...
Oh, God! Oh, God! Oh, God!
만지지 마, 모니카가...
No, don't touch that.
내일 만나서
돌려주려고 했는데
Like I wasn't dreading tomorrow
enough, having to give it back.
'안녕, 배리, 나 기억하지?
가족들 앞에서 당신 망신 준 사람'
"Hi, Barry, remember me? I'm the girl
that stomped on your heart. "
반지 돌려줘야 되는데
Now I must return the ring
without the ring...
반지가 없으면
더 힘들어지는데
...which makes it so much harder.
걱정마, 찾아주면 되잖아
찾을 거지?
Easy, we'll find it. Won't we?
- 그럼
- 좋아
Look, it's gonna be okay.
You'll give it back...
괜찮아, 우리가 찾아줄 테니까
다시 돌려주면 되잖아
-...and we'll eat ice cream.
-Okay. It's a pear-shaped diamond--
좋아
작은 다이아몬드가 달렸는데...
알았어
다이아몬드 반지 찾으면 말할게
Any diamond ring we find,
we'll run it by you.
근데 마지막으로 낀 게
언제야?
-When did you have it last?
-Doy, right before she lost it.
호이!
아마 잃어버리기 전일걸
요즘도 '호이'란 말을 쓰냐?
You don't get
a lot of "doy" these days.
아침에 끼고 있었어
I know I had it this morning.
주방에서 분명히...
I know I had it when I was
in the kitchen with--
주방에서 뭘 했는데?
Dinah?
나한테 화내지 마
-Oh, don't be mad.
-You didn't.
- 설마
- 미안해
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-I gave you one job!
겨우 그거 하나 시켰는데
그래도 면발은 쫄깃하단 말야
But look how straight
those noodles are.
모니카, 그렇게 하면 라자냐에 든
약혼반지를 찾을 수 있을까?
That's not how you look
for an engagement ring in a lasagna.
난 못해
I just can't do it.
얘들아
Boys? We're going in.
우리가 쳐들어가자
안녕
Hi.
- 무슨 인사가 그래?
- 캐롤이 임신했대
-That is not a happy " hi. "
-Carol's pregnant.
찾았다!
I found it!
그게 무슨...
What--?
그래
Yeah.
두 시간 동안
나도 그러고 있다 왔어
Do that for two hours, you might
be where I am about now.
베개 갖고 야단법석 떤
보람이 있었나 본데?
That puts that whole
pillow thing in perspective.
어떻게 하기로 했어?
How do you fit into this whole thing?
캐롤이랑 수잔이 나도
관여해야 될 것 같다고 하는데
Carol and Susan want me
to be involved.
싫으면 상관 안 해도 된대
But if I'm not comfortable with it,
I don't have to be involved.
완전히 나한테 달린 거야
-It's totally up to me.
-She is so great. I miss her.
정말 괜찮은 여자야
보고 싶다
관여한다는 게 무슨 뜻이야?
-What does she mean by "involved "?
-Your job is done.
네가 할 일은 끝난 것 같은데
재미도 다 봤잖아
And the most enjoyable.
뭐라고 말 좀 해봐
Phoebe, say something.
내일 초음파 검사하는데
같이 가자는 거야
They want me to go down
to this sonogram thing...
...with them tomorrow.
나도 어떡해야 할지 모르겠어
그냥 레즈비언일 때가 좋았는데
Remember when life was simpler...
...and she was just a lesbian?
그때가 좋았지
Those were the days.
그래서 어떻게 할 거야?
-What are you gonna do?
-I have no idea.
모르겠어
내가 어떻게 하든
난 아빠가 되는 거야
No matter what I do,
l' m still gonna be a father.
어차피 망가진 거잖아
This is still ruined, right?
마타 룩윈의 딸이 너한테
전화할 거다
Martha Lugwin's daughter
is gonna call you.
이 카레는 무슨 맛이니?
-What's that curry taste?
-Curry.
카레 맛이죠
맛있잖아요, 정말요
I think they' re great. I really do.
그 사람들 기억나니?
큰애가 널 쫓아다니지 않았니?
The big Lugwin had a thing for you.
- 누군들 안 쫓아다녔겠어요?
- 엄마도 참
-They all had a thing for him.
-Oh, Mom.
이해가 안 가는데요
걔가 왜 전화를 해요?
Why is this girl going to call me?
이제 막 졸업했는데 음식인지
요리인지를 하고 싶다는구나
She just graduated, and she wants
to be something in cooking or food....
네가 식당을 하고 있다고
내가 말했거든
I told her you have a restaurant--
식당을 하는 게 아니라
식당에서 일하는 거예요
-I don't have, I work in a restaurant.
-They don't have to know that.
그런 것까지 얘기할 필요는
없잖니
오빠, 이리 와서 스파게티
만드는 것 좀 도와줄래?
-Ross, help me with the spaghetti.
-Yes.
그래
스파게티를 하려고?
그건... 쉽지
Oh, we' re having spaghetti.
That's easy.
실은 라자냐 하려고 했어요
We were going to have lasagna.
라자냐 좋지
-I love lasagna.
-We' re not having it.
근데 없어요
그럼 뭐하러 얘길 꺼냈니?
너도 참 별나다
Then why bring it up? He latches on.
나더러 이기적이라고
말할지 모르겠지만
This will sound unbelievably selfish...
레즈비언이니 아기니 하는
얘긴 언제 할 거야?
...but did you plan to bring
up the baby/lesbian thing?
제발 내 열 좀 식혀줘
It might take the heat off of me.
레이첼도 너무했지
That Rachel.
We saw her parents at the club.
걔네 부모님을 만났는데
불쌍해서 못봐주겠더라
They were not playing well.
결혼식에 얼마를 썼는지
말하고 싶진 않지만
I won't say what they spent...
4만 달러면 큰 돈이지
...but $40,000 is a lot for a wedding.
그래도 그 앤 식장에
남자를 버리고라도 왔죠
At least she had the chance
to leave a man at the altar.
그게 무슨 뜻이에요?
-What's that supposed to mean?
-Nothing.
별 뜻 없어
그냥 그렇다는 얘기야
-It's an expression.
-No, it's not.
아니잖아요
네 엄마 말 듣지 마
넌 언제나 독립적으로 살았어
Don't listen to her.
You've always been independent.
피둥피둥 살이 쪄서 친구
하나 없어도 넌 잘 지냈잖니
Even when you were a chubby kid...
...and you had no friends,
you were just fine.
방에 틀어박혀서
혼자 책도 읽고 퍼즐도 풀고...
You'd read alone in your room.
Your puzzles....
세상엔 로스처럼 유난히
잘 나가는 사람이 있단다
People like Ross need
to shoot for the stars.
박물관에도 다니고
논문도 발표하고...
With his museum
and his published papers.
다른 사람들은 현재 위치에
만족하며 지내지
Others are satisfied with
staying where they are.
그런 사람들은 절대 암에
걸리는 법이 없단다
These people never get cancer.
말하자면 자신의 생활에
만족하고 있는 거야
They're happy with what
they have, content...
...Iike cows.
암소처럼
암소라구요?
Cows, Dad?
내가 유난히 암소를 좋아하지
She knows how much I love cows.
괜히 욕심 부렸다간
죽도 밥도 안 되는 건데
I read about women trying
to have it all, and I thank God...
우리 모니카는 그런
걱정은 없으니 다행이야
...our " Harmonica"
doesn't have that problem.
넌 잘 될 거야
-l' m telling you, you'll be fine.
-Thank you, Daddy.
고마워요, 아빠
Oh, so this does work.
되는 거였네
오빠, 요즘 어때?
So, Ross, what's going on with you?
사건 같은 거 없어?
가족들하고 나눌 얘기도?
Any stories? No news, no little
anecdotes to share with the folks?
알았어, 알았어
Look, I realize you guys
have been wondering...
두 분, 캐롤하고 제 얘기가
궁금하실 텐데요
...what exactly happened
between Carol and me.
And so, well, here's the deal.
솔직히 말씀드릴게요
캐롤은 레즈비언이에요
Carol's a lesbian.
수잔이란 여자와 살고 있죠
She lives with a woman named Susan.
지금 제 아기를
임신하고 있는데
She's pregnant with my child.
캐롤과 수잔이 제 아기를
키우겠대요
She and Susan are
going to raise the baby.
넌 다 알고 있었니?
And you knew about this?
너희 부모님 너무 심하시다
Folks are really that bad?
프로다우신 거지
Well, you know, these people are pros.
뭘 하는지 정확히 알고 시간을
끌면서 할 일을 다 하시는 거야
They know what they do.
They take their time.
They get the job done.
부모님을 바꿀 수 없다는 건
알지만
They say that you can't change
your parents.
할 수만 있다면
오빠 부모님이랑 바꾸고 싶어
Boy, if you could, I'd want yours.
오줌 누고 올게
Must pee.
쌍둥이인 것보단 나아
It's worse when you' re twins.
- 너 쌍둥이야?
- 그래, 우린 연락도 안 해
-You' re a twin?
-We don't speak.
일밖에 모르는 타입이거든
She's this high-powered,
driven, career-type.
- 무슨 일을 하는데?
- 웨이트리스야
-What does she do?
-She's a waitress.
닮았니?
-ldentical?
-People say we look alike.
그렇다고들 하는데
난 모르겠어
But I don't see it.
나 가게 문 닫아야 돼
You guys, I kind of
gotta clean up now.
챈들러, 넌 외아들이니까
이런 걱정은 없지?
Chandler, as an only child,
you don't have this.
그렇긴 한데 부모님이 진짜
좋아하는 가상의 친구가 있었지
No, although I did have
an imaginary friend...
...who my parents preferred.
불 좀 꺼줄래?
Hit the lights, please.
내가 얼마나 오래
있었던 거야?
How long was I in there?
가게 정리하는 거야
-l' m just cleaning up.
-Oh, you need any help?
내가 도와줄까?
그래, 고마워
Okay, sure. Thanks.
그렇다치고...
내일 배리 만날 일이 걱정돼지?
Anyway....
So you nervous
about Barry tomorrow?
조금
A little.
많이
A lot.
충고 한 마디 해줄래?
최근에 버림받은 사람으로서
So, got any advice?
You know, as someone
who's recently been dumped.
꼭 '버림받았다'고 표현해야
하겠니?
You may wanna steer clear
of the word "dumped. "
그 친구가 상처를 받았다는
사실을 명심해야겠지
Chances are he's gonna be
this broken shell of a man.
그러니까 너무 근사하게
보이진 마, 물론 쉽지 않겠지만
You should try not to look
too terrific. I know it'll be hard.
우리 이럼 어떨까?
내가 배리한테 반지를 돌려주고
Or I'll go down there,
and I'll give Barry back his ring.
네가 캐롤이랑 수잔하고
초음파실인지 뭔지에 가는 거야
And you can go with Carol
and Susan to the ob-gyn.
- 내일 캐롤 만나는구나?
응
-
You've got Carol tomorrow.
- 일이 왜 이렇게 꼬였을까?
- 그러게 말야
-When did it get so complicated?
-Got me.
- 우리 학교 다닐 때 생각나?
- 그럼
-Remember being in high school?
-Yeah.
그 땐 누군가를 만나 사랑에
빠지면 다라고 생각하지 않았니?
Didn't you think you'd meet someone...
...fall in love, and that'd be it?
- 로스?
- 나 여기 있어
-Ross?
-Yes. Yes.
Man, I never thought I'd be here.
내가 이렇게 될 줄
상상도 못했어
나도
Me neither.
늦어서 미안해, 일 때문에
그 놈의 공룡이...
Sorry l' m late. I got stuck at work.
There was this big
dinosaur thing. Anyway....
안녕?
Hi.
로스, 수잔 기억하지?
-You remember Susan.
-How could I forget?
- 어떻게 잊겠어?
- 로스
안녕, 수잔
악수 좋죠, 좋아요
Hello, Susan.
Good shake, good shake.
지금 기다리는 사람이...
So, we' re just waiting for--?
- 오버만 박사님
-Dr. Oberman.
-And is he--?
- 그 분은...
- 여자분이세요
물론 그렇겠죠
-She.
-Of course, "she. "
우리의 특별한 상황을
알고 계셔?
Is she familiar with our
special situation?
그래, 많이 도와주고 계셔
-Yes, and she's very supportive.
-Okay, that's great.
그거 잘됐군
됐어요
No, l' m-- Oh.
고마워
Thanks.
꽥 꽥 꽥
...
로스
그걸로 자궁을 열 거야
That opens my cervix.
- 배리?
- 들어와
-Barry?
-Come on in.
정말?
-Are you sure?
-It's fine.
그럼, 괜찮아
로비는 몇 시간 더 있을 거야
Robbie's gonna be here for hours.
어떻게 지내?
So, how are you doing?
잘 있어
I' m....
I' m okay.
- 좋아 보이네
- 그래...
-You look great.
-Yeah, well.
파베르 박사님
제이슨이 숨을 못 쉬어요
Dr. Farber, Jason Greenspan 's gagging.
곧 갈게요
조금만 기다려
Be right there. Be back in a second.
내가 찼어
I dumped him.
그래요?
어떻게 되는 거야?
So, how's this all gonna work?
아기가 엄마 뱃속에서
자라고 있으니까...
The baby grows
in a special place inside--
고마워요
그 문제 말고...
우리 관계 말예요
Thank you.
I mean, how's this gonna work,
you know, with us?
중요한 결정을 해야
되는 거 아냐?
When important decisions
have to be made?
무슨 얘기야?
-Give me a "for instance. "
-Well, I don't know.
나도 모르겠어, 좋아
아기 이름은 어떻게 할 거야?
-How about with the baby's name?
-Marlon.
- 말린
- 말린?
아들이면 말린, 딸이면 미니
If it's a boy. Minnie, if it's a girl.
쥐 이름 딴 거야?
As in " Mouse"?
할머니 성함을 땄어
As in my grandmother.
그래도 '미니'하면
쥐 같잖아
Still, you say " Minnie, "
you hear " Mouse. "
줄리아 어때?
How about...?
How about Julia?
줄리아?
-Julia.
-We agreed on Minnie.
미니로 합의봤어요
재밌군요, 평생을 함께 살기로
했으니 상황이 달라졌어요
We agreed we'd spend
our lives together.
Things change.
Roll with the punches.
줄리아도 생각해봐 줘
I believe Julia's on the table?
미안해
Sorry about that.
So, what have you been up to?
요즘 어떻게 지내?
그냥...
Oh, not much.
- 나 취직했어
- 잘됐네
-I got a job.
-That's great.
썬탠했어?
Why are you so tan?
아루바에 갔다왔어
I went to Aruba.
저런, 신혼여행을 혼자
다녀온 거야?
Oh, no. You went
on our honeymoon alone?
아니
No.
사실은...
I went with....
고통스러울 텐데
-Now, this may hurt.
-Me?
- 저요?
- 아니
No.
민디랑 갔어
I went with Mindy.
민디?
Mindy?
들러리 섰던 민디?
My maid of honor, Mindy?
응, 우리 사귀고 있어
Yeah, we' re kind of a thing now.
그러니까...
뭐가 꼈네
You got plugs!
조심해, 빠지잖아
Careful. They haven't quite taken yet.
렌즈를 꼈어?
And you got lenses.
손으로 눈 쑤시는 거
싫어하잖아
You hate sticking your finger
in your eye.
민디는 괜찮대
Not for her.
당신한테 고마워
Listen, I really wanted to thank you.
좋아
Okay.
한 달 전만 해도 당신한테
복수하고 싶었어
A month ago, I wanted to hurt you
more than I've ever wanted to.
세상 누구한테보다 당신에게
상처를 주고 싶었지
난 치열교정사잖아
And I'm an orthodontist.
당신이 옳았어
You know, you were right.
I thought we were happy.
우린 행복한 줄 알았지만
그런 게 아니었어
We weren't happy.
하지만 지금 민디랑은 행복해
But with Mindy...
... now l' m happy.
침 뱉어
- 뭐?
- 저예요
-Spit.
-What?
Me.
그건 그렇고...
Anyway....
이거 당신 반지야
민디가 갖고 있던 거지만
I guess this belongs to you.
Or maybe some day Mindy.
결국 주인이 되는군
Like she'd settle for that.
그래
Yeah, that's true.
정말 근사한 반지야
But I think it's a nice ring...
...and thank you for giving it to me.
나한테 줘서 고마워
돌려줘서 고마워
Thank you for giving it back.
치료 안 해요?
Hello!
헬렌이 뭐가 어때서요?
-Please, what's wrong with Helen?
-Helen Geller?
헬렌 겔러?
이상하잖아요
-I don't think so.
-It's not gonna be Helen Geller.
헬렌 겔러는 안돼
고마워
-Thank you.
-No, I mean, it's not Geller.
내 말은 겔러가 아니란 뜻이야
그럼 헬렌 윌릭?
It'll be Helen Willick?
헬렌 윌릭 번치로 할 거야
No, actually, we talked about
Helen Willick Bunch.
잠깐, 이 여자 이름이
왜 들어가?
Wait a minute.
Why is she in the title?
내 아기이기도 하니까요
It's my baby too.
당신이 정자도 만드는 줄을
몰랐네요
Really? I don't remember
you making any sperm.
그런 말이 어딨어요?
And we all know what
a challenge that is.
두 사람, 그만 좀 해
좋아, 그렇다고 쳐
내 이름도 들어가야겠어
-You two, stop it.
-She gets a credit. I' m in there too.
헬렌 윌릭 번치 겔러라고
해야겠어? 그건 아동 학대야
Helen Willick Bunch Geller?
I think that borders on child abuse.
물론 아니지
겔러 윌릭 번치라고 해
Of course not.
I'm suggesting Geller Willick Bunch.
아니, 아니
이 사람 좀 봐
See what he does? He knows no one's
gonna say all those names.
누가 그런 이름을 부르겠어?
겔러라고 우기는 것 좀 봐
자기 멋대로야
They'll call her Geller.
He gets his way.
내 멋대로?
내 멋대로라고 생각해요?
My way? You think this is my way?
이런 상황에서 내 멋대로란
표현을 써도 되는 건가요?
Of all the ways I ever imagined
this moment being...
이건 말이 안돼요
난 정말...
...this is not my-- You know what?
This is too hard.
오늘은 좀 어떠세요?
메스꺼우세요?
IKnock, knock. How are we? Any nausea?
- 조금요
- 약간요
-A little.
-Just a little.
엄마가 된다는 게 힘들겠지만
나눌 수 있다는 건 감사한 거죠
I was wondering about the
mother-to-be, but thanks for sharing.
누우세요
난 가야겠어
-Lie back.
-You know what? I' m gonna go.
이런 특별한 상황을 더 이상
견딜 수가 없어
I don't think I can be involved
in this family thing.
세상에...
-Oh, my God!
-Look at that.
- 저거 봐
- 그래
I know.
굉장하지 않니?
Well, isn't that amazing?
뭐가 보인다는 거야?
What are we supposed to be
seeing here?
몰라, 지구를 공격하려는
외계인 같아
I don't know, but I think it's about
to attack the Enterprise.
머리를 왼쪽으로 하고 눈 힘을
좀 빼고 보면 푹 퍼진 감자 같아
If you tilt your head
and relax your eyes...
...it kind of looks
like an old potato.
- 그렇게 보지 마
- 알았어
Then don't do that, all right?
모니카, 어떠니?
Monica, what do you think?
감동적이지?
-Are you welling up?
-No.
- 아니
- 맞잖아
감동 받았잖아
-You are. You' re welling up.
-l' m not.
아니라니까
- 넌 고모가 되는 거야
- 그만해
-You' re gonna be an aunt.
-Oh, shut up.
안녕, 민디
Hi, Mindy. Hi, it's Rachel.
나 레이첼이야
응, 잘 지내
오늘 배리를 만났어
Yeah, l' m fine. I saw Barry today.
그래, 얘기 들었어
Yeah, he told me. No, it's okay.
Really, it's okay.
아니, 괜찮아
정말 괜찮아
둘이 행복했으면 좋겠어
I hope you two are very happy.
I really do.
그리고 말야, 민디
일이 잘 돼서...
And, Min, you know,
if everything works out...
너희 둘이 결혼하고
아기도 낳게 되면
...and you guys get married
and have kids...
수술하기 전에 폭삭
가라앉은 코를 쏙 빼 닮게 될걸!
... I hope they have his hairline
and your nose!
유치한 거 알지만
이러니까 속이 다 시원하다
That was a cheap shot,
but I feel so much better now!